film_questions = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Han Solo's co-pilot and best friend, 'Chewbacca', is an Ewok.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The movie 'The Nightmare before Christmas' was all done with physical objects.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet"
                 " in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Shaquille O'Neal appeared in the 1997 film 'Space Jam'", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel "
                 "film of Star Wars during and after filming.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock's film 'Psycho' it is said he used chocolate syrup to "
                 "simulate the blood in the famous shower scene.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, David Prowse was the actor who physically portrayed Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio's character hunts down the killer of his son.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "'Minions' was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
